剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
问你个问题
Can I ask you something?
说吧  老兄
Anything,Pal
你是怎么知道Claire溺水的?
How do you know Claire was drowning?
Claire!
我听到了她的求救
I could hear her calling for help
那你也能听到闪电咯?
You...heard the lightning as well?
我不是在救Claire  Charlie
I wasn't saving Claire,Charlie
我是在救你
I was saving you
当我看到闪电雷击顶棚时你被电死了
When I saw the lightning hit the roof you were electrocuted
当你得知Claire溺水时  你...
and when you heard Claire was in the water...
你想救她  但你自己却被淹死了
You drowned trying to save her
我尽力了  我尽力救了你两次但不论我怎么努力...
I've tried,brother,I've tried twice to save you but no matter what I try to do...
你都是要死的Charlie
You're gonna die,Charlie
你疯了吗?  老兄
You're insane,mate
超人能瞬间环绕地球
Superman can fly round the entire planet in the blink of an eye
伙计  如果是赛跑的话超人是远远比不上闪电侠的
Dude,if we're going by a pure foot race Supes would get dusted by the Flash
为什么超级英雄会参加赛跑呢?
But why would the man of steel agree to a sodding foot race?
估计是为了慈善?
Uh,for charity?
闪电侠一定能取胜他能震动大地并躲过一切障碍物
And Flash would totally win,'cause he can,like vibrate through walls and stuff
震动啊!
Vibration
如果超人面前有一面墙他会怎么做呢?
Well,and what would Superman do if he came against a wall?
他不能打碎它
Well,no smashing allowed
不能飞  不能使用那些超能力
No flying,no smashing
那个比赛还有其他限制吗?
Any other restrictions I need to know about?
也许我们该给超人配个氪星石...
Perhaps we should fit superman with a pair of kryptonite...
什么鬼东西?
The hell?
Claire!
- 不要碰他  - 我的天啊!
-No,don't! Don't touch it.  -My God,my God!
呼吸  尽量呼吸
Just breathe
看上去这像是自制的  我们得回去
Looks like it's homemade.We've got to get back
- 不  你来帮他!  - 我帮不了他!
-No! You help!  -I can't help!
我很抱歉  老兄
I'm sorry,mate
这里  在这里
Here it is. Here it is
超人能瞬间环绕地球...
Superman can fly around the entire planet...
那根电缆在哪里?
Where's the wire?
你是不是吃了不该吃的东西?
Did you eat those mushrooms Jack warned us about?
听着
Listen to me
有根电缆被埋在沙子里
There's a wire,a cable buried in the sand
你知道我在说什么吗?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
又是那些预感  是吗?
This is future crap,isn't it?
这根电缆  你知道它在哪里吗?
The cable! Do you know where it is?
这很重要
This is important
为什么?
Why?
超人
Superman...
因为有个人即将到来
Because someone's coming
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：    许愿
校对： 许愿
■
双语字幕：    七色九天       独翼天使
后期：     梁良      字幕监制：  梁良
■
上帝通过各种方式来考验我们的信念
God tests our faith in many ways
如你所知  我们也有自己的方式
So,as you well know,we have our own test here...
沉默的誓言定能长存
A vow of silence that lasts as long as we see fits
这不仅是挑战人的意志也是在挑战人的信念
This challenge is both one's patience...and his faith
对某些人来说可能要用一周的时间
For some,it may last a week
还有一些人需要一个月
Those we're less sure about,a month
我以前从没认为你会坚持的 ...
Personally,Desmond I never thought you'd last...
但现在我得承认自己错了
and so now I stand corrected
不管是什么原因  你的道路指引你来到这里
For whatever reason,your path has led you here
并成为我们中的一员
And now you're one of us
欢迎你  修士
Welcome,brother
谢谢  修士
Thank you...Brother
早上好Jack
Morning,Jack
在自己床上醒来感觉不错吧!
Must be nice to wake up in your own bed
是啊  家  温馨的家
yea,Home,sweet home
我能借一下急救箱吗?
So I was wondering if I could borrow your first aid kit
我的脚扭了
I've...twisted my ankle
- 要我看看吗?  - 不用了  谢谢
-You want me to take a look at it?  -No,you're all right
- 我自己包扎过了  - 好吧
-I've taped my share of ankles. -Right
谢谢
Thanks
有什么不对劲吗  Hurley?
Something wrong,Hurley?
没事  只是...
No,just...
继续让Desmond和我们在一起
keeping Desmond here company
因为我们是朋友了
'cause we're friends
- 别忘了还我  行吗?  - 当然
-Bring that back when you're done with it,okay?  -Absolutely
你刚才都讲了些什么?
What the hell was that?
你想引起他的怀疑吗?
Do you want him to get suspicious?
怀疑什么?
Suspicious of what?
比如那时你知道Claire要淹死  是吗?
Oh,this is like when you knew Claire was drowning,isn't it?
你要急救箱就是为了保险一定有人会受伤
That's why you got the first aid kit.Someone's gonna get hurt
- 是我吗?  - 不是  以防万一罢了
-Is it me?  -No. It's just a precaution
伙计  你不是要我带你去找电缆吗?
Look,dude,you want me to take you to the wire?
你给我个合理的解释
I want an explanation
我看到了一连串事情...即将发生的事情
I saw a sequence of events...things that are gonna happen
你看到了什么?
What did you see?
就像一块拼图  只不过我还不知道那图案是什么
It was...It was like a sort of jigsaw puzzle only I didn't have the picture on the box
我还不知道要怎么把这些拼凑起来
so I don't know how the pieces fit exactly
但其中的一块  那第一块...
But...one of the pieces,The first one...
就是你把电缆从沙子里拉了出来
It was you,pulling the cable out of the sand
那其余的部分呢?
So what are the other pieces?
如果我告诉你的话图案就会被破坏
If I tell you that,it'll change the picture on the box
那又怎么样?
So what?
我们要做的不就是阻止坏事发生吗?
Isn't that the point...Preventing something bad?
这次不是
Not this time
这么说你不想阻止那些事的发生...
So you're not trying to stop something from happening
你想让它顺其自然
You actually want it to happen
胜过一切
More than anything
雀斑女  你在吗?
Hey,Freckles,you home?
你不是被禁止叫绰号了吗?
Thought you weren't allowed to use nicknames
我赌的时候你不在场所以你不算
well,You weren't around when I lost the bet...so you are
怎么了?
What's up?
想问你件事
I wanted to ask you something
什么事?
yea?
我人在这呢!
I'm up here
你告诉他了吗?
So did you tell him?
我告诉谁什么了?
Did I tell who what?
你知道的
You know
告诉医生啊
Did you tell the doc...
我和你的事
about you and me?
没有  不过他知道了
No.But he knows
他在那些监视器里看到我们了
He saw us on one of their surveillance monitors
你不是说那些都坏了吗?
You said the camera was broken
他们还有一个
Well,they had another camera
真是群变态
Perverts
不管怎样他知道了
Anyway,he knows
既然大家都知道了
Well,now that...that's outta the way...
不如来点午后乐事?
How about a little afternoon delight?
我是说做爱
That means sex
等等  雀斑女
Come on,Freckles,wait. Now...
要我给你做集锦磁带吗?
Do you need me to make you a mix tape?
好啊  为什么不呢!
Yeah,why don't you do that?
你再告诉我一遍  伙计
Dude,you're gonna have to tell me again
我们需要Jin干嘛?
What do we need Jin for?
因为那时他和我们在一起
Because he was there with us
在海滩上  我发现电缆的时候?
On the beach,when I find the cable?
在这里...
This way. Here it is
是的
That's right
那些都在你的拼图里?
In one of your puzzle flashes?
没错
Aye
如果他不来的话  那个人也不会来了?
So... If he doesn't come then neither does the someone you won't tell me anything about
应该是这样
That will be the long or short of it
真不知道怎么才能说服他
but I've no bloody idea how I'm gonna get him to come with us
看我的
Watch the master
- 野营?  - 没错
-Camping?  -Yeah
海滩上的篝火  嚼着棉花糖  躺着看星星
you know,like,sleeping under the stars,fire on the beach,marshmallows
野营
Camping
好啊
yes
人人都爱棉花糖
Everybody likes marshmallows
好极了  带上水和吃的
Good man. Get food,water
你去哪里?
Where are you going?
我们还需要一个人
We need one more
你以为我是白痴吗?
How daft do you think I am?
这才不是去野营
This isn't a camping trip
你又看到什么了是吗?
You've had another one of your visions,haven't you?
这次是什么?
What was it this time?
有人要来这座岛
Someone's coming to the island
到这里来?
Coming?
有新人要到这里?
As is someone who's not already here?
到底怎么回事?
How the hell is that gonna happen?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you
难道和我没关系吗?
It's got nothing to do with me?
和Jin  Hurley一样你也和我们在一起
Well,you're a part of it,yeah,as are Jin and Hurley
不过你之前并没告诉Jin和Hurley他们会死
Right,but with all due respect you haven't previously told Jin or Hurley
他们不会死的至少这次不会
that they're gonna die. Well,that's not gonna happen,not this time
我能带上吉他吗?
Can I bring my guitar?
当然
Absolutely
好吧  算我一个
All right,I'm in
我刚才还有点担心
You had me worried there for a second
就是这里
This is it
你怎么知道?
Well,how can you tell?
我就在这里顺着电缆走进丛林的
'Cause that's exactly where I followed the wire into the jungle
那它在哪里?
Where is it,then?
干得好  伙计
Way to go,dude
在这里
Here it is !
信号灯就落在这边的斜坡上
The beacon fell this side of the rise
不过那次我顺着这根缆线走进丛林时
Just one thing,last time I followed this wire into the jungle
差点被Rousseau的机关串成烤肉串
I almost got kebabbed by one of Rousseau's spiky death trap things
把她弄下来
Cut her down
我们现在不进丛林  还不是时候
We're not going in the jungle!Well,not yet
已经很晚了  今晚就在这里扎营吧
It's getting late,so,we'll camp here tonight
野营
Camp
他们什么时候来?  你的那个神秘人物
So when do they get here...your mysterious someone?
快了
Soon
你现在可以自由的说话了  Desmond修士
You do realize you are free to talk again,brother Desmond?
大概沉默无语的时间太久了吧
Used to being quiet,I suppose
Moriah葡萄园
修士们给这里的葡萄酒取名真有意思
I find the name the brothers have chosen for the wine made here...interesting
为什么?
And why is that,brother?
Moriah是座山的名字  是Abraham杀死Isaac的地方
Well,Moriah is the mountain where Abraham was asked to kill Isaac
不是个好地方吧?
It's not exactly the most...festive locale,is it?
但上帝宽恕了Isaac
And yet God spared Isaac
可能有人会说上帝用不着让Abraham
Well,one might argue that...God need not have asked Abraham
牺牲自己的儿子了
to sacrifice his son in the first place
那就不是考验了  是吗?
Well,then it wouldn't have been much of a test,would it,brother?
也许你低估了牺牲的价值
Perhaps you underestimate the value of sacrifice
Desmond修士  Desmond修士
Brother Desmond!
我在门口碰到这个人 他有话要和你说
I met this man waiting at the gates
He says he needs to have a word with you
很抱歉
Sorry,sir
请宽恕我  修士
Forgive me,brother
麦片真美味
The oatmeal's awesome
是啊
It is,huh?
很奇怪不是吗?
It's strange,huh?
怎么了?
What's that?
回到了这里  不再想方设法逃出笼子
Being back,not...looking for a way out of a cage
不再因为一些事而冲进森林
not finding a reason to go running off into the jungle again
真不知道该怎么做
I almost don't know what to do with myself
享受这些吧
Well,enjoy it
我敢肯定马上又会出事的
I'm sure something will go wrong soon enough
今晚我的冒险就是要去海里洗盘子
Well,my big,dangerous adventure for tonight
is gonna be doing the dishes in the ocean
- 小心点  - 我尽力吧
-Well,be careful  -I'll try
- 借我用下勺子好吗?  - 没问题
-Can I borrow that spoon?  -Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks
- 晚安  - 晚安
-Good night.  -Yeah,good night
你不敲门吗?
What,my doorbell busted again?
你要干吗?
What the hell are you doing?
闭嘴
Shut up and don't talk
- 你哭了?  - 我说闭嘴!
-You crying?  -I said shut up!
好吧
You got it
我喜欢说小鸟的那段  伙计
Dude,I love the part about the bird
是只小鸟吧?
It was a bird,right?
- 到你了  - 我?
-You.  -Me?
你听说过那个夜海怪兽吗?
Have you heard the one about the chupacabra?
怪兽?
Chupa?
像一只长刺的熊  但墨西哥人...
Yeah,it's like a bear with spines but Mexican...
谢谢
Thanks
那是谁?
Who's that?
她叫Penny
Her name's Penny
真漂亮
That's not bad,Des,not bad at all
你怎么会离开她到这里来的?
So how did you manage to leave her behind and come here?
因为我是个懦夫
Because I'm a coward
抱歉
Sorry
你和我都一样  老兄
You and me both,pal
我想逃避她  但她却一直在找我
You know,I tried to run away from her,and she...She tracked me down
她说只要有钱和决心  她能找到任何人
"With enough money and determination you can find anyone," she said
我整夜想着她说过的话  也许她真的不会放弃
You know,I used to get through my nights thinking that she actually meant it,that she never gave up...
也许这3年来她一直在...
that maybe she spent the last three years...
寻找我
looking for me
那是什么?
What's that?
是直升机吗?
Is that a helicopter?
救援队
Rescue
那是直升机的声音吗?
Is that how a helicopter's supposed to sound?
不是
No!
- 我们得去那里  - 去那里?
-We gotta go out there.  -Out there?
- 是啊  - 为什么要去?
-Well,yeah.  -In what?
我们得做些什么
Well,we gotta do something
快看!  看啊!
Look.Look!
我的天啊!
My god
不  伙计  那不是空投食品
No dude,it's not a food drop
你也看见那个信号灯了
You saw the beacon thing
好像有人被弹出来了
Someone,like,ejected
可那是架直升机啊!
Yeah,but that was a helicopter
怎么会从直升机里弹出来?
You can't eject from a helicopter
也许是跳下来的
Well,maybe they jumped
关键是他们已经着陆了
All that matters is that they're here
他们?  也许根本就不是人
"They"?How do we even know it's a person?
因为他说"有人"要来这里
Because he said "someone" was coming
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
去他们的着陆点
Out to where it fell
快  我们走
Come on. Let's go
不  慢点
No,slow down
我们可不能半夜里到丛林里去
We're not gonna trudge out into the jungle in the middle of the night
我们必须得去
Yes,we are
Hurley提到Rousseau的陷阱时你没有听到吗?
Were you even listening to Hurley when he mentioned Rousseau's death trap?
再过2小时就天亮了
Now it's gonna be light in two hours
- 我们可以等到...  - 她不能等
-We'll wait until...  -She can't wait
她?
She?
他们
They
不管是谁...
Whoever it is...
可能已经受伤了
could be hurt
我们4个现在就得出发
We have to go all four of us now
为什么?
Why?
因为这都是本该发生的
Because that's the way it's supposed to happen
是吗?  看来真的要发生了但我还是不会走的
Right. Well,I guess it's supposed to happen without me
超人
Superman...
那么天一亮就出发...
We'll leave at first light,then...
我们一起
together
好极了
Terrific
你妹妹在家吗?
Is your sister in?
马上
Leave.
离开
Now
让他进来  Derek
Let him be,Derek
你好  Ruth
Hello,Ruth
你现在是个修士了?
So you're a monk now,aren't you?
准确的说我还是个初学者  但是院长说...
Well,technicallyI'm still what they call a novice till the abbott says...
你来这里干嘛Desmond?
Why are you here,Desmond?
既然你问起...
Well,now that my initiation is done...
我觉得我还歉你一个解释
I felt like I owed you an explanation
Desmond
你这样做已经来不及了
You can never begin to explain what you did
你在婚礼前1周离开了我
You left one week before the wedding
婚礼都安排好了
Everything was planned,bought and paid for
你却突然消失了
You just disappeared completely
我收到了召唤
I had a calling
我们恋爱了6年
We dated for six years
那期间你最接近宗教那次 还是因为凯尔特人队赢了冠军杯!
and the closest you ever came to a religious experience was Celtic winning the cup
是的  我对婚礼的事感到了恐慌
Yes,I was scared about the wedding
也许当时我喝多了
so I had a few pints,too many,maybe,I had
我抬起头
I raised my eyes
问自己"我在做正确的事吗?"
and asked,"am I doing the right thing?"
这是我记得的最后一件事
And that's the last thing I remember
当我醒来时
And when I woke up
发现自己躺在马路上
I was lying on my back in the street
我不知道怎么会在那里
and I don't know how I got there
有个人站在我身前
And there was this man standing over me
他伸出手问我"我能帮你吗  老兄?"
and he reached out his hand and he said to me"can I help you,brother?"
我第一眼就注意到他腰间系着的绳子
And the first thing I noticed was...the rope tied around his waist
我看着他  然后...
and I looked at him and...
我明白了...
I knew...I knew
我注定要随他而去
I was supposed to go with him
我注定要抛下...
I was supposed to leave...
所有我关心的事
everything that mattered behind
为了这次伟大的召唤
Sacrifice all of it...
我要牺牲一切
for a greater calling
幸好不是该死的牧羊人召唤了你
Well,it's a good thing a bloody shepherd didn't help you up
否则你就要和羊一起生活了?
or I suppose you'd be off with the sheep,wouldn't you?
下次和别人分手的时候  Des
Next time you want to break up with someone,Des
别去什么修道院
don't join a monastery
只需要告诉她  你该死的害怕了
Just tell the girl you're too bloody scared
你到底是医生还是木匠?
You a doctor or a carpenter?
你父亲从没教过你怎么用锤子?
What,your dad never taught you to use a hammer?
没有  可我爸倒是教会了我喝酒
No,my dad taught me how to drink
至少那也算个本领
Well,at least it's something
没打扰你们吧?
Hope I'm not interrupting
你们在争论谁是最佳另一半吧?
You two arguing over who's your favorite other?
你想干吗  Sawyer?
What do you want,Sawyer?
我想...医生
Oh,what I wanted,doc
自从你离开以来事态有些变化
was to inform you there's been some developments
since you were A.W.O.L
告诉我
So tell me...
你的反手怎么样?
how's your backhand?
哪来的桌子?
Where'd you get the table?
你没认出来吗?
Don't you recognize it?
舱口爆炸时弹出来的啊
It fell out of the purple haze when the hatch went blammo
如果我们每隔108分钟不玩一次
If we don't play every 108 minutes
这座岛会爆炸的
the island's gonna explode
你也有弱项啊!
Finally,something I can beat you at
要知道我从12岁起就没再打过
You know,considering I haven't played since I was 12
这没什么可骄傲的
I wouldn't be too proud
多少?  18分?
What is that,18 point?
是啊
yeah.
很奇怪不是吗?
It's kinda strange,huh
回到这里
being back?
很好笑吗?
Something funny?
Kate昨晚在厨房说了同样的话
Kate said the same thing in the kitchen last night
是吗?
She did?
是啊
She did
19分
19 point
你们一起吃饭的吗?
So you guys ate together,huh?
不  昨晚我和Juliet在一起
No,Juliet and I had dinner together last night
三局两胜?
Best two out of three?
好啊
You got it
接下来呢?
So what's next?
接下来?
Next?
是啊  你看到了电缆  从天而降的那个信号
Yeah,you saw the wire,the flashy thing falling out of the sky
接下来呢?
Now what?
- 也许我能帮你...  - 够了
-Maybe I can help you find...  -That's it
接下来就这样了
There is no next
我们要找的就是那信号灯
We find the beacon
你为什么要骗我  伙计?
Why are you lying to me,mate?
伙计  到现在为止我已经救了你3次
Look,mate,I've saved your life three times now
如果你还不信任我的话那我就没辙了
If that hasn't bought me your trust,I don't know what will
快走吧
Let's move
伙计
Dude...
我都快发心脏病了
seriously,I'm gonna have a coronary
你没有  如果你再不走的话
Actually,you're not,and if you don't get a move on
我们黄昏之前就到不了那里
we're not gonna make it before nightfall...
看看这个
Look at this!
肯定不是Rousseau的
It can't be Rousseau's
否则我早就被石头砸死了
If it was Rousseau's,a massive rock would be flying at my head right now
别动
Don't move
- 你干吗?  - 别动
-What are you doing?.  -Don't move
这些是和那东西一起掉下来的吗?
Did that come down with the flashing red light thingy?
对讲机
Walkie-talkie
不  那是卫星电话
No,dude,that's a satellite phone
糟了  没电了
Crap,it's dead
这很正常
Shocker
我的天啊
My God
那是你吗?
Is that you?
那她又是谁?
Then who's she?
她叫Penny
That would be Penny
这是什么?
What's this?
你的集锦磁带
Your mix tape
你到底要不要啊?
Well,you gonna take it,or ain't you?
"Phil Collins精选集?"
"The best of Phil Collins," huh?
别挑三捡四的了
Don't get picky
如果Bernard问起来  就说我什么也不知道
And if Bernard asks,I don't know a thing about it
谢谢你  James
Thanks,James
昨晚你为什么要那么做?
So why'd you jump me last night?
什么?
What?
是因为你看到医生和Juliet在一起吗?
Was it 'cause you saw the doc hanging out with Juliet?
不是那样的
It was not like that
不是吗?
It's not?
想要利用我吗?  雀斑女
You ain't gotta use me,Freckles
到时你开口就行了
All you have to do is ask
你认为是她  是吗?
You think it's her,don't you?
谁?
Who?
你女朋友  Penny
Your girl... Penny
你认为那直升机里的人就是她
You think it's actually her who bailed out of the helicopter
本来我希望是这样
Earlier I hoped it
现在我知道是这样
Now I know it
你为什么不早点告诉我们?
Why didn't you tell us?
我说了你还会来吗?
Would you come if I had?
当然会
Of course
为什么不来呢?
Why wouldn't I?
我不告诉你们是因为...
I didn't wanna tell you because...
我不想改变什么
I didn't want anything to change
也对
Fair enough
如果你的预感能让我们得救
Look,if whatever you're seeing leads to your girl getting us rescued
我们干嘛要去改变呢?
why would we want to change anything?
是吗?
Right?
是啊
Right
多谢提醒我们带雨伞  伙计
Thanks for the heads-up about bringing an umbrella,dude
It's a grand old team to play for
and it's a grand old team to see
and if you know your history
Desmond修士?
Brother Desmond?
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
看来我是被这美酒醉倒了
Well,I believe I'm...getting pissed on our lovely wine
这瓶酒可值100多镑
That bottle of our lovely wine fetches over 100 quid
我们今年只装了108箱
We've only bottled 108 cases this year
我们在做贫穷宣言吧?
It's just as well we've taken a vow of poverty then,isn't it?
我们也做了慈善宣言
We've also taken a vow of charity
是啊
Right
我有种感觉Desmond你不适合当一个修道士
Something tells me,Desmond,that you're not cut out to be a monk
你要知道我这一周过的很不顺利
Well,you know,I've had a tough week
对于这酒我很抱歉
I'm sorry for the wine
我会忏悔的
I'll take the penance
对你来说忏悔还远远不够  Desmond
I'm afraid you're beyond penance,Desmond
Desmond修士
Brother Desmond
不再是了
Not anymore
你要赶我走?
Are you firing me?
是这样的
I am indeed
你不能这么做
You can't do that
我听见了召唤
I heard the call
这一点我很确定
I'm sure you did hear the cal
但这座修道院不是你落脚的地方
but the abbey clearly isn't where you are meant to end up
上帝对你的安排不止是做个修道士  Desmond  他对你有更大的安排
I have little doubt that God has different plans than you being a monk,Desmond...bigger plans
当然是这样
Aye,sure he does
的确是这样
He does
一直以来你都不知道自己该去哪里
You've just spent too much time running away to realizewhat you may be running toward
那我现在该怎么办?
What am I supposed to do now?
听天由命吧
Whatever comes next
Penny是谁?
Who's Penny?
她是Desmond以前的女朋友
She's a chick Desmond used to date
他现在认为她从天上掉了下来
and now he thinks she fell from the sky
所以我们要去救她然后她就能帮助我们得救
So we're gonna go save her life,and she's gonna get us rescued
伙计  就算我会说韩语  你也不会明白的
Dude,even if I spoke korean,it wouldn't make any sense
少废话  我们快走
We'll move faster if we stop talking
她可能受伤了
She might be hurt
我们已经尽全力了
I'm moving as fast as I can
伙计  我可不是闪电侠
In case you haven't noticed,dude.I'm not exactly the Flash
闪电侠太没用了
The Flash is pathetic
你对史上最快的人有意见吗?
You got something against the fastest man alive?
你疯了  伙计!
You're insane,mate!
超人能瞬间环绕地球
Superman can fly around the entire planet in the blink of an eye
伙计  如果是赛跑的话超人是远远比不上闪电侠的
Dude,if we're going by a pure foot race Supes would get dusted by the Flash
为什么超级英雄会参加赛跑呢?
But why would the man of steel agree to a sodding foot race?
估计是为了慈善?
Uh,for charity?
闪电侠一定能取胜他能震动大地并躲过一切障碍物
The Flash would totally win,'cause he can,like vibrate through walls and stuff
震动啊!
Vibration!
如果超人面前有一面墙他会怎么做呢?
And what would Superman do if he came up against a wall?
他不能打碎它
Well,no smashing allowed
不能飞  不能使用那些超能力
No flying,no smashing
那个比赛还有其他限制吗?
Any other restrictions I need to know about?
也许我们该给超人配个氪星石...
Perhaps we should fit Superman with a pair of kryptonite ballet slippers...
什么鬼东西?
The hell?
Charlie快躲开!
Charlie,duck!
伙计
Dude
这边走
This way
不  那信号落在山的那边
No,the beacon fell this side of the rise
不  在那边
No,there
我们分头行动吧
How about we split up?
我和Charlie去那边  你和Jin走另外一条路
Me and Charlie'll go that way.You and Jin go around
我们等会儿在那边山脊上会合
and we'll meet up at that ridge over there
你和Jin吧
You and Jin
我和Desmond走
I'll stick with Desmond
你叫我"快躲开"
You said "duck."
什么?
Sorry?
你大喊"快躲开"
You shouted,"duck."
你知道的  你原来就知道的
You knew,even before we set off
- 你一直都知道的  不是吗?  - 是啊
-You knew all this time,didn't you?  -Aye
那你为什么什么也不说呢?
Then,why didn't you say anything?
如果我告诉你你就不会来了
Because if I told you the truth,you wouldn't have come
你需要我一起来  因为我是你预感的一部分
Oh,you need me to come'cause I was part of your vision
你以为唯一救回你女朋友的方法就是朝我头上射箭吗?
You thought the only wayyou could get your girl back was if took an arrow in the head
你想要牺牲我
You were gonna sacrifice me
如果那个信号不是我原本看到的那样
If the flashes don't happen exactly as I saw them
只要有一点变化
the picture changes
我本该让你死的  Charlie
I was supposed to let you die,Charlie
那是什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
现在已经毫无意义了
It means it's bloody pointless
我不断救你  这样又有什么好处呢?
I keep saving your life,and what good has it done?
只会不断的再次发生
It's just gonna keep happening again and again
也许这样才有意义
Maybe that's the point,yeah?
这也许是个考验
Maybe it's a test
就像上帝考验Abraham  不同的是我失败了...
Like God testing Abraham,except I failed...
因为我打破了预感
Because I changed what I saw
你能听见我吗?
Hey,can you hear me?
伙计  她没反应
Dude,she's not moving
我很抱歉  Penny
I'm sorry,Penny
我很抱歉
I'm sorry
我还以为你会不辞而别
I was afraid you'd left without saying good-bye
不会的
No
我差点想把这也带走了
I nearly took this with me
你不急的话  Martin修士几个小时后要进城
If you're not in a hurry,brother Martin's heading into town in a few hours
你可以搭他的车走
He can give you a ride
但你得做些体力活
That is,if you don't mind doing some heavy lifting
十个箱子都装满了
All ten cases are ready to go
Desmond的是最后一箱
Desmond there is just getting the last one
谢谢  我父亲已经寄出支票了吧?
Thank you,and my father sent the check in advance?
感谢他的慷慨解囊
And please thank him for his generous donation
很高兴见到你
Always a pleasure to see you
再见了  Desmond
Good-bye,Desmond
我想全部都装到后车厢里
I think we should be able to fit it all in the back
如果装不下就放在前面吧
and if not,we'll put the rest in the front
可以吗?
Is that all right?
当然
Absolutely
你最好小心点开车 小姐
You'd better drive safe,miss
这些酒都是很精贵的
This vineyard only makes a limited number of these cases each year
是吗?
Is that so?
是啊
Aye
因为修道士都很懒
It's because the monks are lazy
要知道葡萄果冻比葡萄酒好做多了
You know,it's easier making grape jelly than wine
你怎么这么了解这里的修道士?
And how do you know so much about monks?
我曾经是个修士
I'm an ex-monk
是吗?
Really?
昨天是最后一天
As of last night
我被除名了
I was fired
这可不好笑
Well,it wasn't that funny
抱歉  我只是不知道...
I'm sorry. I've never... I've...
修道士也可以除名的
I didn't know monks could be fired
当然可以
Oh,they can
他们用自己的话告诉我
You know,I was told in no uncertain terms
这座修道院不是我的落脚点  只是...
that the abbey wasn't where I was meant to end up.just a...
一个中转站
step along the path
上帝对我有更大的安排
You know,God allegedly has bigger plans for me
我觉得你不怎么相信这一套东西
Something tells me you don't entirely believe that
是啊  所以我很怀疑
I suspect that's because I don't
他们也许是对的
Well,maybe they're right
如果你不被除名  我们就不会相遇
Well,just think,if you hadn't gotten fired,we wouldn't have met
那我怎么可能到Carlisle  自己搬这些箱子呢?
and then...how could you possibly help me unload these crates in Carlisle?
我有说过要陪你去Carlisle吗?
Did I say I was coming to Carlisle with you?
目前还没有
Not yet
如果一个前修士已经有某个安排了....
I mean,of course,if an ex-monk already has plans...
要知道我一般不搭陌生人的车
You know,I don't usually get into cars with strangers
那样的话  我叫Penelope
Well,in that case,I'm Penelope
Penny
Desmond
很高兴见到你  Penny
Very nice to meet you,Penny
她还活着!
She's alive
退后!
Stand back!
都闪开!
Get away from her!
我在这里
I'm here
我在这里  Penny
I'm here,Penny
让开  Charlie
Just get off,Charlie
我很抱歉  Penny
Sorry,Penny
我很抱歉
Sorry
Desmond?
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■